Contact

B.Mallenahalli.KBidare(post).Kadur (tq). Chikmagalur (dist) 8867710169 (Mobile) sunilms1010@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ sunil-247792167 (LinkedIn) github.com (Personal)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
Machine Learning
Deep Learning

Languages

Kannada (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)
Hindi (Professional Working)

Certifications

Data Science

Machine Learning

Data science

Honors-Awards

Secured First place in national level Badminton competition

Secured 4th place in SGFI (school games federation of India) in Badminton competition.

Sunil M S

Data Analyst at Bharat Electronic Limited Bengaluru

Summary

Highly passionate Data Analyst having 1.5 years of experience with extreme analytical curiosity who loves to play with data mine valuable insights for the company .I'm skilled in Python, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Statistical Modelling, MySQL, Pyspark and visualisation tools

Experience

Bharat Electronic Limited
Data Analyst
February 2019 - Present (1 year 7 months)
banglore

tech vibz Data Science Intern September 2019 - January 2020 (5 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Bosch Data Science Intern January 2018 - August 2018 (8 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Education

Visvesvaraya Technological University
Bachelor of Engineering - BE · (2014 - 2018)

Javawar Navodaya Vidyalaya 12, Science · (2013 - 2014)